{
   "name":"Capitals",
   "cards":[
      {
         "question":"Alabama",
		 "answer":"Montgomery"
      },
      {
         "question":"Alaska",
		 "answer":"Juneau"
      },
      {
         "question":"Arizona",
		 "answer":"Phoenix"
      },
      {
         "question":"Arkansas",
		 "answer":"Little Rock"
      },
      {
         "question":"California",
		 "answer":"Sacramento"
      },
      {
         "question":"Colorado",
		 "answer":"Denver"
      },
      {
         "question":"Connecticut",
		 "answer":"Hartford"
      },
      {
         "question":"Delaware",
		 "answer":"Dover"
      },
      {
         "question":"Florida",
		 "answer":"Tallahassee"
      },
      {
         "question":"Georgia",
		 "answer":"Atlanta"
      }
   ]
}